…A Comedy Chiller
Haunted Honeymoon is a comedy, horror, mystery film directed by Gene Wilder.
Radio personalities Larry Abbot and Vickie Pearle are stars of a mystery show.
Since they announced their engagement, Larry has been plagued by speech problems and, seeking out an
unconventional cure, he returns to his boyhood home, a mansion in the countryside, bringing Vickie along.
Larry reunites with numerous family members, but discovers that there are
sinister things afoot within the walls of the creepy estate.
Larry Abbot, played by Gene Wilder.
Vickie Pearl, played by Gilda Radner.
Aunt Kate Abbot, played by Dom DeLuise.
Charles Abbot, played by Jonathan Pryce.
Sylvia, played by Eve Ferret.
Pfister, played by Bryan Pringle.
Haunted Honeymoon is a 1986 American comedy horror film starring Gene
Wilder, Gilda Radner, Dom DeLuise and Jonathan Pryce.
Wilder also served as writer and director.
The title Haunted Honeymoon was previously used for the 1940 U.S.
release of Busman's Honeymoon based on the stage play by Dorothy L.
The film was distributed by Orion Pictures through a deal with HBO.
It flopped, grossing just short of its $9 million budget and receiving negative reviews from the critics, while
DeLuise earned the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Supporting Actress for his performance in drag.
The film was both Radner's final feature film
appearance and Wilder's final film as director.
The film explores themes of monster, lightning, fight, magic, drag queen.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.